Okay. Coached by Holly, 94 posts,
1,400 followers.
Pretty early on, 94 posts. That
is an important thing.
So the fact even here
that it looks like you're using a
professional camera, rate
it. Six week mobility program now live.
Okay, don't mind this.
When it comes to you having a sales page
like this, or what we call a VSL.
Would love a video sales letter.
I'd love a video front
and center just to explain
what it is that I'm getting.
So for instance,
if you go to my business mentorship
website, link's in the description.
Let's pick anything.
Short-form content mastery.
There's always a video just front
and center that's
going to explain what it
is specifically that you're going to get.
Because some people
are going to land on your page,
and they're going to want to
read the text. Some people
are going to look at the images.
Some people are going to watch the video.
Some people are going to look at
absolutely everything.
So it's important
that we have something for everyone on
that.
Now, even if I go to another one, there
is not one of these where I don't just
explain what the course
is in layman's terms.
So wherever it is
that we're going to put something,
especially if we've got a
purchase price of 75 pounds,
I would love to have a video here just
explaining
what it is.
Because I might land on this page,
it's Monday morning, I'm thinking,
"Cor, that's a lot of text," and I'm gone.
But not terrible.
Coaching inquiry, Strava. Nice.
Let's have a look at some of your videos.
Now, you say online coach with a peach,
so I assume that you're looking to
help people develop the bootay.
So I don't mind that too
much,
but you are kind of desexualizing
yourself.
But if it works, it works.
Like sugar on my tongue, tongue, tongue.
Your body is so sweet, sweet, sweet.
Okay, so seated good mornings,
pretty underrated exercise.
Think here you could've explained a bit,
like the music's cool, yeah.
Maybe I would've just wanted Holly to tell
me what the hell I'm doing here.
If you come.
And we could've started this definitely
with a hook.
If you're someone
that gets a sore lower back from doing
good mornings, if you're
someone that wants to challenge your
hamstrings and glutes.
Some of you may have seen this exercise
and not known what it is or what it's for,
because really it's a hip hinge exercise
where we're stabilizing the pelvis to help
you extend the hips.
At LLC,
we're going to be working in phases.
We'll-
Okay, so I like this talking to camera.
Big fan of this. Let's go back again.
At LLC,
we're going to be working in phases.
Okay, no hook. So, at LLC,
So we haven't really established what LLC
is, and if this was to go to people that
didn't follow you,
they just wouldn't know what's going on.
And we've always got to assume
that our reels on social media
are being put out to
people that follow us, to people
that aren't.
Now, these ones, going out to people
that don't follow you,
are gonna tank because
people are like, "Who's this?
What's she talking about?
Don't know," gone.
But we sometimes need our content to vibe
with the audience that we're
trying to build. So
if it goes to a cold audience,
and they don't vibe with it,
it's not really gonna get shown to any
more in the audience.
We'll be going from strength to hybrid,
and with a sprinkle of conditioning, too.
So we-
So don't you think this should've been in
a sales page, or maybe even email
marketing?
These kind of discussions about
if you're trying to promote your
services, don't do this here.
We want to use social media to build
engagement, get
awareness,
get people to vibe with our brand.
Then we want to take them away from social
media.
So we don't really want to sell here so
much.
You might get a few nibbles,
but it's better off done away from social
media.
Hello. Hello. It's me. Hi,
every-
Just no context, really. Like I said,
under 100 posts, great.
But again,
why would someone do a single leg RDL?
Which side do we load the weight on?
What should the tempo be?
What could this help people with?
What areas is it targeting?
What problems is it solving? Your job
is to solve problems.
And again, although some women
are gonna be like, "Go get it,
girl boss," if you
solve people's problems from the off,
you're just gonna have such a better time.
The reason you're failing to stick to the
gym is because you're setting unrealistic
goals and expectations for yourself.
If you think you're gonna start with five
days a week at 6:00 a.m., but then you
get up for your alarm and maybe-
Let's just get into it a little bit
quicker. All right, Holly, not bad.
Some things to work on.
If you start all of your posts trying to
solve a
problem, I think you could do better.
Talking of solving problems, there
is an area over here
that Declan won't show you
in the edit. It'll probably be blurred.
These are all people
that send me their social media so I can
critique it.
There's gonna be a link in the description
to this video. Click that.
Pop in your email address.
I'll add you to the list. I will be kind.
Next. Right.
Adajaba11. Boxing coach. All right.
I actually quite like this niche.
I think there's a lot of people out there
that kind of could do boxing.
I've got a heavy punch bag over here
that I never really use. I like punching.
I'm not a boxer.
But helping men build fighter bodies
and mindsets.
Don't hate it. Rebel.com.
That's rebel.com.co. Selling punch bags.
I actually don't hate this,
because I sometimes always think about
getting someone
to buy a punch bag,
then they have to use it,
and follow a program.
Let's get into the reels.
Consistency, consistency, consistency,
man. That's the name of the game, bro.
If you-
Just trying to look cool.
You're just getting trending audio
and boxing around in
the dark and stuff.
Don't ever let somebody tell-
Using motivational quotes. Yeah,
but what are you doing with this?
Let's open with some issues. How to jab,
how to cross, how to throw a hook,
how to hit a bag.
What's the difference between punching a
bag
for becoming a better boxer,
or punching the bag for building a boxer's
physique? What about skipping?
What about cardio? What about nutrition?
You talk so much about building a
fighter's physique,
but you don't actually talk.
So these are the things I want:
benefits of having a punch bag,
where to set up a
punch bag at home,
freestanding punch bags,
hanging punch bags.
What kind of weight requirement would you
need for a punch bag bracket?
Can you get water punch bags?
Can you get a bob punch bag?
There's so many things here
that I'm glad you're a boxing champ,
but if you want to
help men build fighter bodies
and mindsets,
then why the fudge do you not do it
in your content? You know what I mean,
brother? Next.
J Sims Coaching. If you're in the UK,
there is a mad discount
on Nutonic at the moment on TikTok Shop.
I'll put a link anyway. J Sims.
J Sims. Right.
I want you to just have your bloody name
here, J
Sims. I help people sculpt a body.
Because I feel already a little bit
disconnected. What's your name? Juliet,
Janice.
Today to improve your physique and your-
Structure and accountability.
Here's three things you can start doing
today to-
Quite softly spoken,
so we're gonna always have to have
that in mind when you have
music. Probably just don't have the music,
and one thing we're probably gonna need
is some kind of good audio.
Structure and accountability
are the two things keeping me-
No hook. Structure and accountability.
It's a statement.
It's not really a hook, though.
What is up? My name is Julia.
Julia. Is that the first one I said?
Or did I say Juliet? I don't know. What
is up?
That is a question. It's a hook,
but it's kind of like an American one.
That's a nice hook.
What is up? My name is Julia.
I'm a certified personal trainer and
an online fitness-
By this point, they don't care.
They've gone, I'm afraid.
Free 15-minute consultation for online
coaching. This is not where it goes.
What is up?
No one's gonna watch this.
No one's gonna book in.
So again, if you
were to put out loads of really,
really helpful content, then were
to put out a lead magnet,
get people's information,
you could then email all of
your database going, "Hey,
next week I've put five 15-minute slots
free in the
diary. If you want them, grab them."
It makes me wanna
Who does this help?
Maybe 25 people dish you a like, but your
job, Jay Sims, and change that to Junior.
Your job is to help other people,
not to talk about yourself.
"60 seconds,
six reps today on incline dumbbell." No
one cares.
RDLs while giving you some tips
and tricks for yours.
Whenever we're doing RDLs or Romanian
Okay, we just-
[upbeat music]
Okay, let's
take the double gun poses out of this
because ultimately, very, very
rarely are people going to come to you
and go, "Oh, my God, I saw your double gun
pose. Can we work together?"
And again, talking about a pump. What
are you trying to do?
You're just trying to impress other PTs.
The perfect clients for you will not go,
"Oh, my God, I saw your pump."
Here's a full day of eating things
that I enjoy while-
"Here's a full day of eating,
what I'm going to eat
while I'm trying to do
something."
Okay,
this has to change as quick as possible.
You say you help sculpt a body
that people feel comfortable in.
All you seem to do
is make content about yourself
and tense to the camera.
And you may be a very humble, nice person,
but this just screams that you love
yourself.
And then you want to work together at
Google Docs.
A Google Docs. Hmm. Come on.
I want you to do me a favor. For the
next month,
you are banned about posting about
yourself.
You are only to put out content that's
going to help your perfect demographic
with
something they're struggling with.
We're going to change this picture to
something a little bit more
brand-focused, not just you,
because here you're admiring yourself.
And if everything comes across as
self-centered, I'm not going to hire you.
So you are just going to start with hooks.
Your hooks could be,
"If you struggle with this movement,
if you're struggling with
this outcome,
if you find it hard to this outcome,"
solution, solution,
solution.
I want your content buckets to be
nutrition, training.
I want you to go after fallacies,
things that people believe
that aren't true.
And then the fourth thing I want you to do
is react to people saying things that
you disagree with.
So there's four content buckets for you.
Good news is, shouldn't be too hard.
Why is everyone on this flipping list a
bloody trainer?
Look, I don't mind doing fitness stuff.
It's where I've earned me crust.
But can you lot who are watching this,
if you're not a PT, please sign up to
that list because I don't want to deal
with just personal trainers forever.
I've got potential.
I don't want to be the PT business guy.
I can help other businesses. Okay.
Good transformation.
This should be on your landing page. This,
hmm.
Harry Hughes, personal trainer,
online coach. They know, bro. They know.
Got PT in your name. Transformations.
What? What? What does that mean?
Get rid. SoCal Gym, Paul. Cool.
DM for more info or click
link to start today.
No one's starting from your Insta page,
mate.
Again, we need a lead magnet. People
are going to go to your website.
They're not going to give you their email.
Domain not configured, brother.
Domain not configured. Come on, man.
Fucking hell.
Bro, admin,
sort your fucking yourself out, mate.
You know what I mean? Jesus Christ.
I just wanted to make that clear with
that video.
"I just wanted to make
that clear with that video." What a
terrible use
of the opening three seconds.
If you enjoy-
And are you driving, brother?
Are you driving?
You look like you could be a passenger
here
... or the optimal style of training,
then 100% go ahead,
do the optimal training.
I hate content in cars. It's low quality,
it's low effort.
It's like, "Oh,
I'm just going to talk to camera
while I'm in my car." Nah, mate.
If you want a chest like Arnold,
you have to do this exercise.
Hmm, don't know if I like this hook.
If you want a chest like Arnold,
do this exercise.
You could've said instead...
Well, it's like me pointing to a nice car.
If you want a car collection like this
rich person, then do this with your stocks
and shares. Hmm.
This could've been more investigative
journalism. You could've been like,
"Arnold Schwarzenegger
was known for having one
of the best chests in the world,
and although he was on
performance-enhancing
drugs,
there was actually several things
that he did to develop such an amazing
chest. And in this video,
we're going to go through them."
Obviously, that's not true. For example,
with this converging chest press,
I love it. However,
a lot of people will come on this and not
find it too enjoyable, therefore-
Bored. Sorry.
[singing]
Bored. You've not even moved the weight,
and I'm bored.
Don't be afraid of using the smaller
plates for progressions.
On dips.
1.25 kg every-
On dips
... session soon adds up.
If you do it for a long enough-
Bored
...
guess when to add weight to their sets.
Here's what I do instead.
Bored.
[singing] Fuck any bitches
that came out of Milano.
Bored.
No.
Don't care.
This is where most chest days go wrong.
Barbell press, dumbbell press,
then machine press.
All three-
You're taking too long to make your point.
This is what annoys me
... they're basically the same movement,
hitting it flat.
So-
So your hook here should've been,
"Is dumbbell bench press, bench press, and
plate-loaded chest press the same
movement?" Straight away,
we know what it is.
B-roll, B-roll, B-roll.
Then you come into it and go, "Surely,
if we're starting
with the weight here
and finishing with the weight here,
it's the same outcome."
Well, no. Let me explain.
Then go into each one, boom, boom, boom.
There's not enough urgency.
There's not enough care
and attention for my time being
sacred here. It's just a bit,
"Did you know?" You sound like Nathan
Joseph.
Your warmup could be making you weaker.
Here's how to effectively warm up for a
heavy leg press.
Start-
Again,
I just think your opening thing here
should've been like, "If you want to do
heavy leg press, make sure you do this."
All right. One plate for eight slow reps,
pausing at the bottom, focusing
on full range of motion, and get-
Boring. No offense. It's just boring
... your warmup-
Who's going to go, "Mate,
I found this guy online, Harry Hughes,
mate.
Yeah,
so he was telling me I need to be doing a
warmup set on the leg press.
One plate a side, eight second eccentric.
Mate,
it changed my life." It's not
life-changing content, mate.
This is the exact leg workout I've been
using to build s-
Mate, don't make it about yourself.
If you're someone looking for a leg
workout to do this to your legs, then I
recommend you do this, rather than,
"This is something I've been doing for my
legs
for the..." Make it about them because
unfortunately, mate, they don't care about
you. Even this video right now,
no one cares about me. It's fine.
All they care about is the expertise
that I can share with them.
And if I give them enough expertise,
if enough people watch these videos
and go,
"Wow, James,
that's really insightful," then they might
think they like me, but
they don't.
They just like the information
that I'm giving them.
They like the feeling
that they get from learning from me.
It's not personal, mate.
This just needs to be better. Like I said,
we caught this early. Only 242 posts.
That's fine. Next. Ooh. Oh. Is this
Someone that isn't a personal trainer. Oh,
flooring.
Oh. Okay. Nationwide Flooring Company,
court marking, wood floor sanding
and maintenance. Love it. Great.
One thing I'd be keen to know about would
be if
there's a team of you or
if there's one person, because
if you're the main guy, it
could be like Joe, Baseline Flooring,
and then everything could be about Joe.
But let's have a little look.
This has got... Do you know what?
I was just about to say,
this has got viral potential. 10 million.
Oh,
I do hope to God you've done this again
since.
And again, we can have a hook here.
Have you ever wondered how the lines end
up on
a basketball court?
Love is killing my...
And you could raise the stakes with this
and be like, "One false move and I've got
to redo the whole thing."
Tonight.
While chasing the clouds away.
Because this is fucking brilliant, mate.
Look at this. Okay. Right, mate.
If you haven't fucking done this,
I'm going to lose it.
If you long press this, people
are going to want to know how you get the
tape to
curve. Oh, it's quite easy, mate.
Basically, you get the tape,
and you do this.
"What type of paint do you use?" Again,
answer this.
"Be careful,
two-centimeter wrong paint
and it'll pour some.
Way too many lines on
that court." You know what I mean?
What do the lines do?
You could even do a video about what the
lines do.
[spray painting]
I think we need a bit of personality,
a bit of voice behind.
You wind me up.
Because this is something
that everyone can relate to.
You're getting millions of views here,
500,000.
Just the way you fuck me up.
I just want to hear some talking. Why
are you doing this? I would love to know.
So really interesting niche here.
Are you getting bookings through here?
I bloody hope you are. Oh,
TikTok. I bet it slaps over here,
doesn't it?
Yeah, you're getting millions of views.
So what I want is a bit of fucking
personality behind it.
Let me show you
something. This is the pool guy. Now,
this guy, if we watch his stuff,
and you Accute.
Okay, that's an ASMR one. Fuck's that?
So this is granular shock,
and I use this all the time
when pools go green.
So this is granular shock. Use this
when pools go green. That's a hook.
A really high,
unstabilized level of chlorine
which will kill the algae and help
bring the-
Then when he says,
"Kill the algae," what we're actually
waiting for is the-
Pool back to a nice blue color.
This chemical that I'm using is flock.
Quite a lot of the time, I'll use
that just after I've put the shock in as
well.
This helps to combine all the floating
part-
I'm learning
... es in the pool,
leaving the water crystal clear,
and usually works within 24
hours, so I can come back the next day
and vac the pool to waste.
Now we want to know what happens the next
day.
Next up are these pucks, which
are stabilized chlorine tablet,
and they're slow
dissolving.
When they go in the water,
there's just something so oh, about it.
They'll either go in the skimmer,
or they'll go into a chlorine feeder.
And it's only an issue
if it's going in your skimmer
if the pump is lift off for a
long period of time. Stop whinging.
Then we've got stabilized-
So this is the kind of thing I want you to
imitate
All right.
I've got another lazy spa hot tub to clean
out and-
That voiceover is going to be the thing
that takes your business to the next
level,
because I kind of feel like I know this
guy. What's his name?
Don't even know his name,
but I feel like I know him.
If I was to hear his fucking voice on
Radio 1, I'd go, "That's the fucking pool
guy." Let's get that into your content
pronto, please, sir.
And then I would love to know a bit more
about the amount of bookings you get.
So if you're watching this in the
comments, let me know.
But oh my, do you know what, mate?
It would make me so happy to see a
business that
was different,
because you could have a little bit of a
funnel here. I don't know.
You could even sell the tape or something.
I'm not sure how you would quite scope
that.
But there could be a YouTube video in
that as well, millions of views.
Have you ever wondered how you get tape on
a basketball court? Okay, here we go.
Elvie, not a fan of this brother.
Are you wearing gloves in the gym?
Tensing.
Again,
"I help people build muscle." It looks
like you just care about yourself
building muscle, which
is a bit of a problem.
Use a Gmail account.
What are you, part-timer, bruv?
Let's get into it.
Take your picture just to frame it on the
wall.
So you can make mistakes-
Stop this.
Take your picture-
I'm going to do a bit of appeal to
authority here. I hope you don't mind.
My name's James,
been a personal trainer for eight years.
Got an all right rig.
But in the middle of this,
you don't see me like...
[sighs]
Because you'd just be like, "This guy
is a fucking bellend," is what you
would think, isn't it? So because of that,
please just refrain from doing this
because the only people you're impressing
are not people that are going to give you
money. Where was I? A personal trainer.
Had about 118,000 clients go through my
app,
which is pretty good. There
are loads of fitness plebs richer than me.
Joe Wicks made more money than me.
Courtney Black's made more money than me.
But I get a good life. Got my own gym.
Going to have a sauna after.
Got a studio upstairs.
That's where we sometimes film.
Just thought I'd do it down here today.
911 GT3. I do all right.
And I say this from a place of love.
There would be no way in hell that I
would have over 100,000 paid clients
if it wasn't for that, mate.
If it wasn't for the fact
that I didn't do that. What's going on,
bro?
Oh, you made it like this. When
are you going to make some content about
me,
bro?
Again.
Talk to me, brother. I want to hear you.
I want to know you, brother.
All the folks who
were smart back in school,
they didn't know that I was dumb.
Come on, man. I want to get to know you.
I want to get a bit of your personality
across. I feel like we're not getting it.
I want to hear you talk, "Yo, what up?
It's Elvie.
This is what we're doing today.
We're doing this." We need to
communicate with people, brother.
We need to talk to them.
We need to become friends,
and we need to stop obsessing about
ourself and content.
Let's go a couple more. Okay,
we got a big, big hitter.
Okay, Connor Lunder, 30,000 followers.
All right, let's have it. Okay,
with a physique like that, I'll permit it.
Now,
I hope that you coach dudes doing this.
So this is permitted because this
is high level.
Whether you've got your IFBB, JBFF,
whatever it is, I'm not sure. Swoldemort.
Absolute Swoldemort. Quadzilla. All right.
So physique coach, prep coach.
I'll take that.
This month's ESN order,
because I actually can't remember what-
Yeah. So blood testing for me is vital.
You're taking risks with bodybuilding,
as people know
I like this type of content
...
it's a sport where you're putting your
health at risk, and if you're going to
be willing to do that, you ought to
I'd love a YouTube video explaining about
this, why bodybuilders need to check
their bloods once a month.
What issues does bodybuilding cause?
Even if you're going to go through
different things like masteron,
primobolan, what
they do to your lipids, what
that means to your health,
blood pressure monitoring,
stuff like that.
I think there's definitely more to talk
about here.
Do you know what I would like, mate?
I'm not the biggest Jeff Nippard fan,
but he's very good at taking his knowledge
and putting it into videos.
So for yourself, right?
Knee sleeves, belt, hack squat, doing
that many plates to side.
You telling me you've got no knowledge you
could be sharing with me with this.
You're here, first time using this hack,
very nice bit of kit.
Tell me about it.
There's going to be people right here
watching this that are
going to be like, "Wow,
I wish I had the confidence to use
that bit of equipment."
Talk to me about the little locks
and the hands and stuff like that.
Yes, sir.
[grunting]
Right.
Train to failure. Why
are you training to failure?
I just feel like there could be some
education in this.
Unless you just make money from
endorsements.
You say here you link for coaching.
Do you know what I've not seen across any
of your content is any coaching advice?
Anything.
It's just videos of you training.
Why don't you fucking teach me something?
Do you know who I love, right?
I might as well just wank him off at this
point. Ben Yanes.
So you come onto his profile,
and every single video and
post helps you understand something you
didn't-
If you're like me
and millions of other people,
you've probably had shoulder pain
with regular dips.
Look at this.
Look at this for a variation.
Fucking awesome.
You can never look at dips again after
this. Let's have a look here.
Here's an actual rotator cuff workout.
Lovely.
Just every single video,
there's a bit of nuance, there's a bit of
education. Every time I'm watching this,
I'm just thinking about stuff and
learning.
I think every coach should aspire to have
a bit of Ben Yanes in it.
Like here,
we're going to talk about leg length
and squats
Anyone with relatively shorter femurs can
keep the line of force of the bar
directly over their midfoot fairly easily
while still keeping their torso upright.
Watch what happens
when we increase the length of the femur.
When the length of the femur increases,
we have to move the torso back with the
hips.
But now look what happens to the line of
force of the barbell.
It actually moves behind the foot.
So in order to not fall backward,
we actually need to lean the torso forward
to
move the line of force over the midfoot
again.
And this is why people with generally
longer femurs-
Amazing. So those of you out there,
have a bit more Ben Yanes about you.
Okay,
we're going to go into the final one,
so I don't miss any sparring or
training.
I'm going to be rocking up to training
half an hour late because of you
guys. Just letting you know that.
Andrew Hodge PT.
"Building faster, stronger,
fitter athletes. In-person or online.
Everyday athlete." You Hyrox
and CrossFitters, you love this term,
"Everyday
athlete." But do you know, I'm sorry,
other CrossFitters and Hyroxes might know
this, but if you want to take on gen pop,
I just don't think they know what that
means. But anyway,
let's get into your stuff, brother.
If this comes up on my Explore,
I'm skipping past it.
[upbeat music]
Oh my God,
did this guy just share with us his
workout?
Oh my God. Babe. Babe, come out.
Come over here, babe.
Babe,
there's a guy called Andrew on the
internet, and he's sharing his workout
with us. Oh my God, he's put it into ABC.
Has this guy got a fucking PhD in...
Oh my God.
Has this guy got a PhD in strength
and conditioning? This is unreal.
Babe, come on, come over here.
Andrew's sharing his workout.
Oh my God. Upper body strength as well.
That's insane.
That is
fucking... That's mad, bruv. Oh, shit,
bruv. That's so sick.
Prepping delicious high-protein meals for
your week should be easy.
Just like this diced beef prep I fired
together yesterday.
I had this big bag of veg,
so I decided to make use of the-
This is the best one so far, mate.
I actually really like this
... potatoes and the carrots.
By the way, hashtags, they do nothing,
I'm afraid.
After cubing them up,
I fired them onto a baking tray with a
little olive oil and
seasoned with garlic powder
and five spice.
Cool.
You know sharing your workout does fucking
nothing for you or your
business. There is no one out there
that woke up today that wanted a workout.
There's no one that woke up
that wanted a recipe with veggies.
All right?
People are waking up, they're fat,
they're depressed, they're nihilistic.
They just broke up with their partner.
They're getting divorced,
and they haven't had sex in a year.
There are people out there with genuine
problems.
They don't know whether they should be
tracking their calories.
doing fasting.
And I just need you to make it your job to
fucking help those people.
And I want you to help 95% of them for
free,
which is why I need the content to be
better.
Because if you help 1,000 people out
there, trust me, you'll have 50
clients.
To develop their strength
and their running simultaneously,
but it's probably
because they're taking on too much all at
once.
But here's the good thing, strength
and endurance-
More of this
... the most scenic run routes ever,
right at my doorstep, and I thought-
I think
that I've just found the easiest
and best slow- This
is one of the hard truths of
training that I think
that a lot of people struggle to grasp.
I spend a lot of time droning on,
on Instagram
Oh, someone got a new mic
and they did not do their mono- You don't-
...
stereo settings right.
I've only got audio on one ear.
It's just quite generic.
They are actually training because they
think it's going to- Save this video for
later if you're looking for a-
Mate, stop with these fucking workouts.
You're killing me.
Right,
I need you to write down specific problems
that your coaching clients are
facing, because imagine this.
I've watched 10 of your videos.
I could not, if you said, "James,
for a million pounds,
tell me a problem that one
of his clients has faced recently," I
couldn't.
It's just about you and your workouts.
No one's coming to you for online coaching
through this, I can tell you right now,
because all you're doing
is sharing workouts.
We need to make this better.
Your content needs to be specific around
that.
And you also need to appreciate this.
These videos may work for other bigger
creators,
but no one knows who the fuck you
are. So you need to use problems that
are familiar or things that are familiar.
You could even do things on bits of
equipment that are found in the gyms
because
then they would have something to connect
to.
But when it's you just talking about your
stuff, you got to appreciate no one knows
who you are and no one cares.
So you need to break through that.
Everything you talk about needs to have a
problem that they face at the front of
their mind.
You need to give people a reason to not
swipe away.
And I'm here, mate, potentially. If I
was to say the right thing right now in
front of you, that's three grand for me.
Three grand straight up in my pocket.
Thank you very much. So if anything,
I care about your content more than
anyone because three Gs,
and I can't relate with any of it.
And every single video makes me want to
go, "What's next?" But the thing is, I'm
going through your content,
going from your video to your video,
and I'm
getting nothing. But other people,
when they see your content,
are just seeing one
of your videos, and they're swiping away,
and it'll take them to someone else's.
And when Instagram serves your videos to
hundreds of people, that it does, because
it will,
and the majority of them have no interest
or no care about what you're
talking about,
Instagram will gauge your content
and platform as shit.
So we just need to change that.
We just need to make better content, mate.
And yeah. What I need you to do
is comment on this video.
I want you to tell me your exact avatar,
the exact problems they're facing, and
five things that you've had breakthroughs
with, with your clients recently.
And if you can't, if you say, "These
are the five things I've worked with my
clients recently to get them
breakthroughs," and they've not been in
your content
for the last 30 videos, that's a problem,
and that's a disconnect. So yeah. Right.
Those of you that want to be on one of
these videos, click on the link in the
description.
There's also all of my paid stuff,
all of my free stuff.
Those of you,
no one here today had a lead magnet,
and I'm going to put links
for my lead magnets in here. Even
if you don't feel fully...
I'll show you quickly. Even if we go to,
let's go to this video
here. In here, on those links,
there'll be lead magnets.
And even if you don't feel like they're
super specific for you,
just sign up so you
can actually see how a good converting
lead magnet works.
This one's done over $700,000. $700,000 of
attributed revenue. So give it a go.
All right. Sign up.
Speak to you guys in a bit. Bye-bye.